<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, ParseStarterProjectActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Viewd</string>



        <string name="ptr_pull_to_refresh">Pull to refresh</string>
        <string name="ptr_release_to_refresh">Release to refresh</string>
        <string name="ptr_refreshing">Refreshing…</string>
        <string name="ptr_last_updated">Updated: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">Viewd</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Welcome to the Viewd App Beta!
        This beta was launched to test the transparency among android devices and get some feedback from users.
    The app does not currently have picture deletion so make sure the pictures you are uploading are meant to stay! </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_disclaimer">Viewd Beta</string>
<string name="dis">YES THIS IS BORING BUT YOU SHOULD READ IT NOW! END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT: THIS IS A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND VIEWD APPLICATION. You hereby agree that your
use of the software acknowledges that you have read this agreement and agree to it bound by its terms and conditions. (1) Viewd grants you a limited
, revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to use the app sole for your own individual use. You agree to not resell or make any
commercial use of the application. (2) You may not make any changes to this particular application and its internal APK files. (3) You agree
the intellectual property inherent in the application is property of Casey Software Group and Viewd application respectively. (4) Limitation of
Liability: Viewd is not responsible for any type of potential damage caused by the applications mechanics itself. (DO NOT POST SOMETHING THAT
YOU ARE HESITANT ABOUT, IT MAY NOT COME DOWN FOR A CONSIDERABLE AMOUNT OF TIME - THIS IS BETA LAUNCH) (5) This app will be goverened in accordance
with Virginia state law. (6) You understand that this app uses and displays your geolocation upon uploading images. BY CONTINUING YOU AGREE TO TERMS AND CONDITIONS. NOTICE: IF YOU PRESS "SAVE" AFTER TAKING A PICTURE IT WILL IMMEDIATELY UPLOAD TO CLOUD! If you need support please email "viewd.app@gmail.com"</string>





</resources>
